bioaxial.com 2016-06-30

# Privacy Policy - BioAxial – Super Resolution Live

## 1\.      Personal data

1. The corporate pages of the [www.bioaxial.com](http://www.bioaxial.com/) website are compliant with the French Data Protection Act, to the exclusion of any other law.

2. In the case that Bioaxial uses personal information and in accordance with Article 32 of the French Data Protection Act of January 6, 1978, as amended, users are informed that Bioaxial, as a controller, processes personal data mainly for the following purposes:

  * management and follow-up of requests for information made by Internet users and their related answers;
  * reporting on the access to the website;
  * measurement of quality, satisfaction and traffic;
  * subscription to the newsletter and direct marketing, including for commercial purposes;
  * management and follow-up of job applications.

3. Fields marked with an asterisk are mandatory; without this data, users may not benefit from all the functionalities offered by the website editor. This information is used to contact users about the services in which they have expressed interest.

4. If users wish to subscribe to the newsletter, Bioaxial will use the name and email address to send the newsletter. Users have the option to provide additional information such as address and phone number to Bioaxial. Out of respect for privacy, Bioaxial provides a way to unsubscribe.

5. If users no longer wish to receive newsletter and promotional communications, they may opt-out of receiving them by: following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing at  [info@bioaxial.com](mailto:info@bioaxial.com)

6. Bioaxial may provide the personal information of users to companies that provide services to help Bioaxial with its business activities such as offering customer service and sending out emails on Bioaxial’s behalf. These companies are authorized to use the personal information of users only as necessary to provide these services to us.

7. Bioaxial will share the personal information of users with third parties only in the ways that are described in this legal notice. Bioaxial does not sell personal information to third parties. Some collected data may be communicated to partners for direct marketing purposes. The collected data are intended for the website editor and its partners.

8. Users are informed that they have a right to access, interrogate and rectify their data allowing them to rectify, complete, update, lock or erase their personal data if inaccurate, incomplete, equivocal, expired or whose collection, usage, disclosure or storage is prohibited.

9. Bioaxial will respond to the request to access within 2 months.

10. Users also have a right to object to the processing of their data on legitimate grounds as well as a right to object to the processing of their data for the purposes of direct marketing.

11. Users can exercise these rights by sending a letter to Bioaxial:

either by mail together with a copy of a document proving their identity and signature, at the following postal address:

_BIOAXIAL_  
 _40 rue de Paradis, 75010 Paris, FRANCE_

or by email at the following e-mail address:  [info@bioaxial.com](mailto:info@bioaxial.com)

12. Should users fail to respect the provisions of the French Act No. 78-17 of January 6, 1978, they are liable to be penalized. 

13. Users must abstain, in particular, in the case of personal data, to which he or she has access, from any collection, misappropriate use and, generally speaking, from any action likely to interfere with the private lives or reputation of people.

## 2\.      Cookies

14. Users are informed that cookies could be placed on the terminal of users when they visit the website, subject to the choices and options resulting from the settings of their browsing software.

15. A cookie is a data block that is not used for identification purposes but serves to record information about the navigation of the user on the website.

16. Users may choose at any time how to express and modify their choice regarding cookies. Most browsers are set by default and accept cookies, but users can choose to systematically accept or reject all cookies or only cookies from certain issuers, by selecting the appropriate settings on their browser.

17. Generally, these parameters can be found in the tabs "tools" or "settings."

18. Users can have additional information:

  * on the website of their browser;  
more generally on the CNIL website at [www.cnil.fr](http://www.cnil.fr/).

19. Disabling cookies may prevent the use of or access to certain features of the website.

20. Users have a right to access, withdraw and modify the personal data communicated via the cookies as explained above.
